Are you that bad that you need to have a
perfect stroke in order to make a ball?
Are you that bad that you need the
perfect warm-up before you can go into a
match? Are you that bad that after one
mistake, you lose all your trust and
confidence that you've been working on
for years? Are you that bad that you
need everybody's approval to feel good
about your game? Are you that bad that
you think you can only perform when you
have your best game at your disposal?
Are you that bad? I don't think so.
Don't fall into the trap that all the
stars have to be aligned for you to get
a win. Use what you've got on the day,
work the process, and get the job done.
Good luck.